(忆往昔)
我们认为可能是始祖
We think it may have been an Alpha.
-什么始祖  -每个怪物总有一个祖先
- An Alpha, like...? - Like all monsters come from somewhere.
抓一个活的始祖给我
Bag me a live Alpha.
-你是吸血鬼的祖先  -始祖
- The first of your species. - The very first.
处理下那一屋子始祖吧  既不能丢下不管
Prison full of monsters -- can't just leave them,
-也不能放了它们  -我明白
- can't let them go. - I understand.
兴隆地产是罗曼公司一部分
Geothrive is part of Roman Enterprises.
迪克又要资助一个考古挖掘项目...
Dick's funding an archaeological dig...
他在沙特阿拉伯的工厂...
Factory in saudi arabia...
和雅加达的渔场...
fishery in jakarta...
-科研中心  -遍地都是
- A research center. - - It's everywhere.
他们是一条绳上的蚂蚱  迪恩
It's all tied together, Dean.
他失控了
He's not in control.
怨魂就是这个样子
That was vengeful-spirit crap.
但他还是鲍比
But it's still Bobby.
你到底是什么
Well, what the hell are you?
我是凯文·谭
I'm a... K-Kevin Tran.
我在读大学预修课
I'm in advanced placement.
他是上帝的先知
He's a prophet of the lord.
那就是神之语了
And that's the word of god?
其中之一  没错
One of them, yes.
那到底写的是什么呢
Well, what's it say, then?
上面写着关于利维坦的事
It's about Leviathan.
有写怎么杀死他们吗
Does it say anything about how to kill them?
若要杀死利维坦
Leviathan cannot be slain
只能用正直凡人之骨
but by a bone of a righteous mortal
浸以三种堕落者之血
washed in the three bloods of the fallen.
上面说我们先要找到堕落天使的血
It says we need to start with the blood of a fallen angel.
我总是愿意为温家兄弟流血
Always happy to bleed for the winchesters.
你好  凯文
Hello, kevin.
(如今)
格洛丽亚·简  为您带来《商业观察》
Business watch with our own, Gloria Jane.
谢谢  菲尔
Thanks, Phil.
现在我们把话题转向农业
And now we turn our attention to agriculture,
一位意想不到的嘉宾
where an unlikely personality
现在已高调来到了直播现场
has now come on to the scene in a major way.
理查德·罗曼  执行总裁
Richard roman, a C.E.O.,
他的公司在国防和航空工业占据主导地位
whose company ominates the defense and aviation sectors,
更不用说他还是励志演说家中的翘楚
not to mention being a giant in the motivational-speaking world.
没办法  格洛丽亚
What can I say, Gloria?
我就是个多面手
I'm a multitasker.
毫无疑问
Clearly.
你最近又通过收购控股了
And now you've recently purchased controlling stock
苏克农业公司
in Sucrocorp --
这是家处于世界领先地位的
among the world's leading manufacturers
高果糖玉米糖浆制造公司
in high-fructose corn syrup.
理查德  很荣幸你能接受我们的采访
It's a pleasure to have you with us, Richard.
请叫我"迪克"
Please. "Dick."
那么  迪克  跟我们说说
So, tell us, Dick,
为什么最近你开始对粮食产业感兴趣了
why the recent fascination with big foods?
人人都知道  我们都爱吃
Well, it's no secret we all love to eat,
不过苏克农业公司关注的是吃得好
but now Sucrocorp will focus on eating well.
请说说两者的关系
Help me connect the dots.
摄入甜味剂怎么让我们变得更健康的呢
How will pumping sweeteners into our system make us healthier?
一个字  纯
One word -- purity.
我们少放食品添加剂
We're dialing back the additives
向全美消费者提供高质产品
to deliver the highest quality all-American product
对得起民众
you people deserve.
美国是进取人士的天堂
America is for go-getters,
亲力亲为  就能创造奇迹
folks who get off their butts and make it happen.
我们力求让您获得健康的身体
And we need you just as healthy as you can be.
所以我们全力以赴
Which is why we are diving whole hog
让美国人更长寿...
into what keeps Americans living longer...
也更美味
and tasting better.
你是说
You do, of course, mean to say
食物会变得更美味吧
the food will be tasting better.
我就是这个意思
That's exactly what I mean.
[邪恶力量 第7季第22集]
你十一点约的人已经在会议室候着了
Your 11:00 a.m. is waiting in the conference room.
谢谢  苏珊
Thank you, Susan.
苏珊...
Susan...
我们还在找主流媒体的代言人吗
Are we still looking for a rep in mainstream media?
-是的  -太妙了
- Yes, we are. - Wunderbar.
去把格洛丽亚"换"下来
Put a "replace order" on Gloria there.
尸体怎么处理
And with the corpse?
打给厨师菲亚
Call chef Fieri.
我想吃烧烤
I feel like barbecue.
凯文  我是迪克
Kevin. Dick.
见到你真让我激动
I'm very excited to meet you.
你很紧张吗
You nervous?
别紧张
Don't be.
我可是你的超级粉丝
I'm your biggest fan.
我给你带了份礼物过来
I brought you a present.
上面说什么  凯文
What's that say, Kev?
我不知道
I don't know.
装得不错
Cute.
埃德加
Edgar?
悠着点  埃德加  别吓坏了这男孩
Easy, Edgar. Don't scare the boy.
我查过你的背景  凯文
You know, I've checked, Kevin.
你是班上的第一名
Number one in your class,
切特·肯尼迪优秀青年科学家称号获得者
winner of the Chad Kennedy Top Young Scientist prize --
还是个神之语的守护者
all that on top of being keeper of the word.
你是个聪明的年轻人
You're a clever young man.
我相信你会做出正确的选择
I'm confident you'll make the right choice here.
不过我明白这是谈判
But I see this is a negotiation.
所以我会加大...筹码
Well, I will sweeten... the pot.
这是什么
What is it?
我的线人告诉我说你在申请普林斯顿大学
My sources tell me you're applying to Princeton.
像我这样的人物给你写封推荐信
Letter of recommendation like that from a man like me --
保你入校
done.
我不能这么做
I can't do it.
孩子  我很欣赏你的勇气
I admire your gumption, kid.
但我还是觉得有商量的余地
But i still think there's some wiggle room here.
这样吧
I tell you what --
我们加大筹码
Let's kick it up a notch.
看看我能不能改变你的想法
See if I can't change your mind.
埃德加  直播信号弄好了吗
Edgar, that live feed up yet?
当然
Of course.
妈
Ma?
妈妈
Mom?!
我想谈判有结果了
Well, I think this negotiation is concluded.
孩子  你真会讨价还价
You drive a hard bargain, kid.
天呐  我读这个的次数
Okay, man, I have read this more times
都超过在爸爸包里发现的那本《花花公子》了
than the Playboy I found in dad's duffel.
是安娜·尼科尔吗
Anna Nicole?
就是安娜·尼科尔
Anna Nicole.
好东西就是没的快
Oh, the good -- they die young, huh?
看这个看到双目流血
Look, we can read this till our eyes bleed.
也看不出更多眉目
This ain't getting any clearer.
好吧  那是什么意思
Okay. Then what does it mean?
斩其首  躯体挣扎凌乱
Cut off the head, and the body will flounder.
-对  -好了
- Yeah. - Okay.
我想我们都同意迪克就是首领  对吗
Well, I think we both agree that the head is Dick. right?
对
Right.
那么  总之  我们去找材料
So, bottom line is, we go grab the stuff,
做成武器
and we mix ourselves a weapon.
就这样了
End of story.
我完全赞同把迪克干掉
Look, I'm all for killing Dick.
我只是说  然后呢
I'm just saying, what then?
我是说  那剩下的利维坦怎么办呢
I mean, what about the rest of the Leviathan?
他们就会...死掉吗
What, are they gonna just...drop dead?
我不知道  也许吧
I don't know. Maybe.
也许
Maybe?
你现在觉得"也许"就够了
"Maybe" is good enough for you right now?
-一个一个来  行吗  -行
- One problem at a time, all right? - Okay.
但是我们横冲直撞之前
But it's not a crazy idea
先探明有没有什么阻碍
to try and figure out what the catch is
不算是很疯狂吧
before we go crashing the gate.
或许这就是那个阻碍
Maybe this is the catch.
上帝不把什么都告诉我们
God's not telling us every detail.
你懂吗
You know?
这可是神之语啊
The word is from god.
你还指望什么
I don't know how much better it's gonna get.
你好  鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
感觉怎样
How you feeling?
前所未有的强壮
Stronger than ever.
你们两个瞎忙活这会儿
Now, while you two have been chasing your tails,
我都在考虑武器的事
I've been thinking on that weapon.
等等  你不觉得你应该省省力气吗
Wait a second. Don't you think you should be savings your strength.
省来干嘛
For what?
我只是觉得你该缓缓
I'm just saying you might want to slow down.
你看上去不太好
You don't look so hot.
我都死了
I'm in the veil.
犀利的日子一去不复返了
My Brad Pitt days are over.
那孩子说杀死利维坦唯一的方法是
Now, the kid says that the only way to kill Leviathan
用淋过三种堕落之血的骨头
is with a bone washed in the three bloods of the fallen.
是人的骨头  利维坦有多饥饿和黑暗
It's got to be from a human as light and good
那人就要有多光明和善良
as the Leviathan are hungry and dark.
好吧  那个好找啊
Yeah. Good luck with that.
其他的能找  现在就能找到
The rest is doable, and doable now.
你已经拿到了堕落天使的血
You've already got the fallen angel blood.
接下来是堕落人类统治者的血
Now, next up is blood from the ruler of fallen humanity.
要我说的话  就是克劳力
Now, the best I can tell, that's Crowley.
第三是堕落野兽之父
Numero tres is the father of fallen beasts.
那是要...
Which means...?
取一个始祖的血
You got to bleed an Alpha.
可他们都死了
But they're all dead.
我们帮克劳力找到的  都赶到了一起
I mean, every one we found, we rounded up for Crowley,
然后小卡把他们全干掉了
and then Cass whammied them all.
那行  就让小卡去解决吧
Well, then, make this Cass' problem, too.
小卡现在没有解决问题的能力  鲍比
Cass ain't exactly in the problem-solving mode, Bobby.
那就找克劳力
Then Crowley!
好吧  我明白了
All right, I get it. I get it.
真的吗
Do you?!
说说而已
I'm just sayin'.
我相信你们俩可以搞定
I have faith that you boys will figure it out.
放心  我没事
Relax. I'm fine.
就是有点激动
Just got a little carried away.
苏克农业公司的宗旨是
Here at Sucrocorp,
顾客的安康至上
your well-being is our number-one priority.
苏克农业公司  吃好  生活才好
Sucrocorp: eat well, live well.
告诉你一声
Little F.Y.I.
鲍比现在在厕所驻扎了
Bobby's officing out of the john these days.
挺尴尬的
Uh...awkward.
这还用说
Yeah, you're telling me.
不过他对于那武器有点想法
He does have some ideas about the weapon, though.
是吗
Really?
没准还真是时候
Well, uh, he may be just in time.
"罗曼购得..."  苏克农业公司是干嘛的
"Roman acquires..." what's Sucrocorp?
他们生产食品添加剂
They make food additives,
也就是高果糖玉米糖浆
namely high-fructose corn syrup.
那东西掺在...几乎什么里面都有
That crap is in -- well, it's in just about everything --
苏打  调味酱  面包
um, soda, sauces, bread.
馅饼不会有吧
Don't say "pie."
馅饼绝对有
Definitely pie.
混蛋
Bastards.
那现在呢
So now what?
罗曼不玩餐馆了
Roman's moved past restaurants?
改玩食品商店  便利店  自动售货机
And into grocery stores, Gas n' Sips, vending machines.
我们能做什么
What can we do about it?
除了对他们的卡车和工厂发动恐怖袭击
Short of going al qaeda on their trucks and plants,
我们什么都做不了
there's nothing we can do about it.
我先前说了  鲍比有点想法
Like I said, uh, Bobby's got some ideas.
[咒语]
两位好
Hello, boys.
你写的是一篇振奋人心的美文啊  凯文
That's some bracing prose you're putting down there, Kevin.
完了吗
You all done?
干得好  普林斯顿大学有你真是幸运
You've done well. Princeton will be lucky to have you.
我妈妈呢
What about my mom?
打电话
Make the call.
放了她
Release her.
强调乱说话的后果
But stress the consequences of talking.
凯文  我要你稍稍再陪我一会儿
Kevin, I'm gonna request the pleasure of your company a tad longer.
而你呢
You, on the other hand,
你要去拜访一位老朋友
I need to drop in on an old friend.
原来那些乱七八糟的符文就是这意思
So, that's what all the "rumble, rumble" was about.
谁翻译出来的
Who translated it for you?
你少管  你愿不愿意给我们血
Never mind. You gonna give us the blood or not?
乐意
Happily.
但目前不乐意
But not quite yet.
我很想剁了迪克
I'm all for chopping Dick,
可我不能让你们带着一瓶我的血到处跑
but I can't have you running around with a vial of my blood, now, can I?
你们知道我的敌人拿到了那些血
You know the sheer number of nefarious spells
可以施多少邪恶的法术吗
my enemies can use that blood for?
-那要什么时候  -到最后
- Well, then when? - Last.
等你们找齐了其他东西后
After you've got all the other components.
我估摸着  天使那边是最难搞定的
Most difficult, the angel part, I'm assuming.
考虑到你们在他们天启里的角色
Given your role in their little Apocalypse,
我难以想象  上头那些唱诗班的
I can't imagine the choirboys upstairs
会为你们献血  给你们...怎么说的
are wetting their vestments to do you -- what's the word? --
帮把手
a solid...
当然了  除非你手里有天使
Unless, of course, you have an angel up your sleeve.
那是挺方便的  不过没有
Well, that'd be convenient, but, uh, no.
不用担心
Don't worry about it.
我们总有办法拿到天使的血
We'll get the angel blood one way or another.
我们下次再找你时你得准备好
We just need you to be ready next time we call.
行
Fine.
提示你们一句
Oh, here's a tip.
我有可靠的消息
I have it on good authority.
还有个始祖活着
There's one Alpha still among us.
消息来源是谁
Whose authority?
我
Mine.
那个吸血鬼始祖够狡猾的
Wily character, that Alpha vampire.
在小卡摧毁了那地方之前
Somehow made good his prison break
他就不知怎的跑了出去
before cass went nuclear on the place.
你是怎么知道的
And you know this how?
亲近你的朋友
Keep your friends close,
更要怎么着你的敌人
your enemies, blah blah.
不用说了  我招子亮着呢
Needless to say, I keep tabs.
他行踪不定
He moves around quite a bit.
不过我有感觉
But I have an inkling
我知道从哪儿开始寻找复活节彩蛋
I know where to start the easter-egg hunt.
祝追踪快乐
Happy trails.
你个混蛋  他在哪
Okay. Where, jackass?!
北达科他州  虎帕
Hoople, North Dakota.
写张纸条不就行了
Piece of paper would have worked.
他生气吗
He seem angry?
生气  他当然生气了
Angry? of course he's angry.
换作你是鲍比  你不生气吗
If you were Bobby, wouldn't you be?
那他有没有显得疲惫
But was he showing signs of fatigue,
或是看着不正常
like -- like fritzing?
不  其实正好相反
No, actually, it was just the opposite.
他说感觉到前所未有的强大
He said he never felt stronger.
我就是担心这样
That's what I was afraid of.
他越是强大
The stronger he gets,
就越是有可能完全变成怨魂
the closer he comes to going full vengeful spirit.
这是事实
That's reality.
我们要商量一下怎么对付他
We need to talk about what we're going to do with him.
-对付他  -是
- Do with him? - Yeah.
三个星期前  你还在说要跟他共处
Three weeks ago, you were talking how this could work.
现在就想让他安乐死了
And now you want to go Kevorkian on his ass?
毕竟传说中还没有与人为善的
I'm just saying that the lore doesn't have a single real-life example
幽灵的先例
of casper the friendly ghost.
基本都是恶作剧鬼  直到猎人过来...
It's all basically poltergeists until a hunter comes along...
传说是个屁
Yeah, well, the lore sucks.
那可是纯怨念啊  迪恩
I'm talking pure hatred, Dean.
没有人性
No humanity.
我是说  他可能杀人  附体
I mean, he could...kill...possess people.
鲍比可以把这栋楼都烧个精光
I mean, Bobby could burn this friggin' building down.
要是他做了出格的事...
Look, if he goes off the rails
怎么
What?
看那边的家伙
Check out that guy over there.
觉不觉得他有点恍惚
He seem a little out of it to you?
我不知道  也许吧
I-I don't know. Maybe.
这边的美食大妈呢
What about Paula Deen over here?
是啊  他们看起来好像...
Yeah, they -- they look like...
像吃火鸭鸡三明治的人
...like those turducken people.
开始了
It's starting.
是玉米糖浆的作用
It's the corn syrup.
店里所有的东西都加了它
Everything in the store is laced with it.
所有的
Everything?
我都要中毒性休克了
Hey, man, I'm gonna go into toxic shock, okay?
我需要路上吃的东西
I-I...I need my road food.
那就正中罗曼的下怀了
That's what Roman is banking on.
这上面写着"天然"  那就没问题了吧
This one says "natural." t-that means it's safe. Right?
真不想打击你
I hate to break it to you,
不过玉米糖浆说白了也是天然的
but corn syrup is natural, technically.
好吧  那我们到底吃什么
Well, then what the hell are we supposed to eat?
太黑了  看不到里面
It's totally dark. I can't see inside.
是不是等到天亮再说
Well, should we wait for daylight?
绝对不行  我们不能等
Hell no, we're not waiting.
我去瞧瞧
I'll scout it.
看有没有必要带重武器进去
See if we need to bring in the big guns.
这不好吧  鲍比
I don't know. Look, Bobby...
好了
Okay.
安全
Place is clear.
但是有些值得一瞧的东西
But there's something you're gonna want to see.
小心点
Careful.
电池酸液也能杀吸血鬼吗
You know a way to kill vamps with battery acid?
我只知道砍头
Only way I know is beheading.
肯定有什么东西能杀掉他们
Well, something didn't agree with them.
看看那面墙
Check out that wall.
你看是不是有些蹊跷
Something seem weird to you?
看看能不能找到开关或者操控杆之类的东西
Yeah, see if you can find a switch or a lever or something.
用不着
Don't need one.
迪恩  把刀收了
Dean. Machete.
我们不会伤害你的
Look. we're not gonna hurt you.
看  没尖牙
Okay? No fangs.
看见没
See?
我们只想聊聊
We just want to talk.
我八岁的时候
I was 8.
妈妈把我留在游戏场  去商店买东西
My mom left me at the playground while she ran to the store.
一个男人走过来
A man approached me
说我是那儿最可爱的女孩
and said I was the prettiest girl there.
之后我就和...
And I've been living with these...
这些东西住在一起
things...ever since.
直到现在
At least until now.
你知道为什么抓你吗
Do you have any idea why?
我是他的"珍馐"
I'm one of his special girls.
其他人负责看好我
All the others, it was their job
时刻准备着迎接始祖的到来
to make sure I was ready for the Alpha, whenever he came.
把我洗干净
Wash me...
每天给我打营养液
Give me my IV bags every day.
我只摄入那个
It's my only food.
这样我的血才纯净
So my blood's pure.
他们这样对你多久了  十二年吗
They've been doing this for, what, 12 years?
处女最美味了
Virgins are a delicacy.
他身边总有一个
He always has at least one of us on hand.
别担心
Well, don't worry, okay?
我们会把你送回你妈妈身边
We're gonna get you back to your mother.
你们认为她还会记得我吗
Think she remembers me?
她当然记得
Of course she does.
你不记得她了吗
Don't you remember her?
这些...
These, uh...
这些人  他们是你朋友吗
These guys -- they, uh, friends of yours?
始祖来的时候他们负责照顾他
They take care of the Alpha when he's here,
不过他们死了
or did.
发生了什么事
What happened to them?
一周前  他们出去捕猎回来  说这次很容易
A week ago, they came back from what they said was an easy hunt.
抓到了三个人类
Three humans just came,
他们都没怎么反抗
didn't put up any fight.
当吸血鬼开始进食时
But when they started on them,
他们都痛苦地尖叫
the vampires screamed in pain.
那几个吸过血的立即就死了
The ones who ate died immediately.
那些没吸的呢
And the ones who didn't?
只有一个
There was only one.
当他看到这种情况时  他就只吸动物了
When he saw what happened, he moved to animals.
他这会就出去捕猎了
He's out hunting as we speak.
从没听说吸血鬼对人类过敏
Never heard of vamps being allergic to humans before.
你说会不会是玉米糖浆引起的
You think maybe it's the corn syrup?
我是说  想想看
I mean, think about it.
加油站的那些人都像吸了毒
The gas n' sip was lousy with stoners.
任人宰割
All ripe for the picking.
她倒是说那次捕猎很容易
She did say it was an easy hunt.
你知道现在始祖在什么地方吗
Do you know where the alpha is now?
说不好  可能知道吧
I don't know. Maybe,
当情况不妙时  他会去一个地方
he has a place he goes when something's wrong.
他说那是他的别苑
He calls it his retreat.
那是什么东西
What is that?
那是萨姆的混蛋跟踪器
That's, uh, that's Sam's douche tracker.
能帮我们找到始祖
Helps us find the Alpha.
我们只需要地址
All we need's an address.
我不知道
I don't know.
但我记得一些事可能能帮上忙
But I remember things that maybe can help.
好吧  你就尽力而为吧
That's okay. Just do the best you can.
你终于回来了
Finally.
我杂志都翻完了
I'd run out of magazines.
问个问题  你老大在哪
Quick question. Where's your boss?
我再问一次
Let's try that again.
-他在哪  -下地狱吧
- Where is he? - Go to hell.
不用了  我住的地方比那儿差远了
No. My neighborhood is worse than that.
蒙大纳州米苏拉市
Missoula, Montana.
有这么难吗
Was that so hard?
我熬不住了  伙计
I can't do this, man.
我不能像个兔子似的活着
I can't live on rabbit food.
我是个战士
I'm -- I'm a warrior.
迪恩  你会没事的
Dean, you'll be fine.
这可说不定啊
You don't know that.
下一步该干什么
So what's next on the list?
如果我们要突袭一个始祖
Well, if we're bum-rushing the Alpha,
我们就得弄些死人血
then we're gonna need dead man's blood,
也就得去停尸房
which means a morgue.
或者...
Or...
或者什么
Or what?
别管停尸房了
Dude, forget the morgue.
现在到处都是吸血鬼毒液
We are swimming in vamp poison.
打扰下  先生
Excuse me, sir. Hi.
我们...我们是...
We, uh, we're with the...
红十字会的
Red Cross.
我们现在血库突然紧张
See, we have an emergency shortage.
我们需要您...
And we're gonna need you to...
你完全听不懂我在说什么是吧
You're not getting a word I'm saying, are you?
胳膊举起来  我们要抽点血
Hold out your arm. We need your blood.
伙计
Dude.
行了  萨姆
All right, Sam.
尽情抽吧
Tap the keg.
就在这吗
Here?
对  萨姆  瞧瞧四周
Yeah, Sam, look around.
这就像伍德斯托克音乐节
It's friggin' Woodstock.
每个人都嗑了棕色酸液
Everybody's hopped up on the brown acid.
我们不用说废话
We don't need the song and dance.
直接扎他就行了
Give him a little prick.
好疼啊
That hurts.
你是说这是为了卡特里娜飓风灾区吗
This is for Hurricane Katrina, you said?
对
Yes.
就是这样
Yes, I did.
那么...
So, look...
等我们到了那儿
when we get there...
怎么了
Yeah?
鲍比不能跟着来
Bobby's gonna have to hang back.
你不同意吗
Do you disagree?
他肯定不答应
He ain't gonna like it.
是他帮我们找到了爱米莉
I mean, he helped us in getting Emily.
我也挺鲍比的  好吗
Look, I'm team Bobby, too. Okay?
但我们把他和爱米莉留在车里是有原因的
But there's a reason we left him in the car with Emily.
你懂的  他越参与行动
You know that.The more action he sees,
他就越容易发疯
the more chance he gets to spin out.
好吧
All right, fine.
我们不让他上前线
So, we'll keep him off the front lines,
那就能保持冷静  继续这样  对吗
and he can just, you know, keep calm and carry on, right?
如果他做不到呢
And if he can't?
他们带你去吸血鬼大本营时
When they hauled you off to vamp camp,
你还记得开了多久的车吗
do you remember how long the drive was?
我们晚上出发的
We left at night.
在日出前到达
Got in before dawn.
那么是六七个小时
So, six, seven hours?
我想是的
I think so, yes.
你还记得上过高速吗
Do you remember any highways?
没有  我们只走小路
No. We only took back roads.
好吧  那就算他们每小时四十五英里
Okay. So, figure they averaged 45 miles per --
应该不会超过三百英里远
Couldn't have been more than 300 miles.
对
Right.
你们走的那个方向
What direction were you going?
我不记得了  很抱歉
I don't know. I'm sorry.
没事的  爱米  你做的很好
Oh, it's okay. Em, you're doing great.
你还记得什么吗
Um...is there anything else you remember?
钟声
Bells.
我们停车时  我听到很响的钟声
As we pulled up, I heard these loud bells.
-当时还没天亮吗  -是教堂吗
- It was still dark out? - You thinking church?
教堂不那么早敲钟
No, that's too early.
有可能是个修道院
It could have been a monastery.
教士早上四点就起来祈祷了
Monks get up at 4:00 a.m. to pray.
又不能泡妞  又不能睡懒觉
Ugh. Can't get laid. Can't sleep in.
真悲剧
A friggin' tragedy.
那么始祖的大本营在花果山旁边(Monk教士和Monkey猴子发音相近)
Okay, so, Alpha's camping next to a, uh, monkey house.
那个范围内有几座
How many do we got in range?
貌似只有一座
Looks like one.
就在
Just outside...
(欢迎来到蒙大拿州密苏拉市)
他就是在这带走我的
This is where he took me.
你确定
Are you sure?
现在怎么办
What now?
我们会带你去一个安全的地方
We'll get you someplace safe.
再绕回来灭了这些吸血鬼
Circle back and ginsu these leeches.
但她就是不明白
...but she couldn't get it.
没错  这就是著名的鸢尾宅邸
Yes, the famous Fleur-de-lis Mansion.
一亿两千五百万的房产
$125 million estate...
好了  走吧
All right, here we go.
10CC吸血鬼毒液
10 ccs of vamptonite.
就这么一说
It's a thing.
卡黛珊是什么
What's a Kardashian?
就是
Oh, that's...
也是个吸血鬼
just another bloodsucker.
没  就开个玩笑
No, it-- it's... a joke.
给
Here.
要是我们黎明还没回来
If we're not back by dawn,
打这个乔迪·米尔斯的电话
call this number, Jody Mills.
她是我们的朋友
She's a friend.
她会照顾你的
She'll take care of you.
来  用这部手机
Here, use this phone.
你得待在这
You gotta hang here.
是为你好  懂吗
For your own good. Capiche?
萨姆
Sam?
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You bet.
风吹的
It was the wind.
冷静一点  鲍比  我们很快就回来
Chill out, Bobby. We'll be back soon.
他好像不太高兴
Well, he didn't take that very well.
你还指望他怎样
How'd you think he was gonna take it?
不好意思
Excuse me.
抱歉
Sorry.
爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
你个小骗子
Why, you little schemer.
不  我就在附近
No, I'm close by.
给你送去了一份礼物
Sending you a present.
这就是迪克·罗曼
And that's Dick Roman.
昨天我向你们介绍了这位美国商界的新星
Yesterday I introduced you to this rising star in American business.
现在  我们将走进幕后
In this hour, we'll go behind the scenes
问出大家几个月来都在问的问题
and answer the question everyone's been asking for months --
是什么让迪克战无不胜
what makes Dick so hard to beat?
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
现在这个时间段
Well, this time of day,
他们大部分都在睡觉
most of them would be catching z's.
他们浑然不觉就被我们拿下
They won't know what hit them.
你在听我说话吗
Hey. You with me?
在
Yeah.
有什么问题
But...
我们就这么冲进去砍头吗
Are you sure you just want to charge in there, machetes blazing?
上一次  动用了一堆猎人才拿下始祖
Last time, it took a dozen hunters to take down the Alpha.
大部分猎人还都死了
And most of them didn't make it out.
你有更好的主意吗
Yeah, well, you got a better idea?
太傻了  蠢毙了
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
迪恩
Dean.
也许我们来迟了
Maybe we're too late.
萨姆
Sam!
在我的家乡
You know, where I'm from,
得牙齿利  爪子锋  才能爬到顶峰
you have to bite and claw your way to the top.
一旦到达巅峰  相信我
Once you get there, trust me,
风景美得不可思议
the view's incredible.
迪恩的生日
Okay, Dean's birthday.
萨姆的生日
Sam's birthday.
可恶
Damn it!
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
-里面没事吧  -我的生日
- Everything okay in there? - My birthday.
有人吗
Hello?
-我需要你的帮助  -离我远点
- I need your help. - Get away from me.
-听着  我得离开这  -求你了
- Listen, I need out of here. - Please!
就借用你一会
Just need you a little while.
抓到那混蛋就放了你
Just till I get the bastard.
温家双煞
The Winchesters.
有意思
I'm intrigued.
爱米莉
Emily.
萨姆
Hi, Sam.
作为在地下室长大的女孩子
For a girl raised in a basement,
你还真会演戏啊
you're a hell of an actress.
你们要伤害我爸爸
You were gonna hurt my daddy.
你真是斯德哥尔摩症候群患者中的奇葩
You get a trophy in Stockholm Syndrome.
真不想煞风景  不过
I'm sorry to burst your bubble, but...
我们没有恶意
we weren't.
萨姆有个更好的计划
Sam here had a better idea.
我们是来谈谈的  仅此而已
We're here to talk. That's it.
是因为我的手下拿走了你们的刀
Now that my guys have taken your blades
和装污血的注射器吧
and your syringes of tainted blood.
是这个意思吗
Is that what you mean?
我们
Well, we...
觉得你也许还耿耿于怀
figured you might hold a grudge.
我怎么会呢
And why would I?
因为你们抓了我  折磨我
Because you captured me, tortured me,
把我出卖给地狱之王吗
sold me to the King of Hell?
其实那是我们的外公
That was more our grandpa.
谢了
Thank you.
真给力
That was awesome.
我要扒掉你们的小白脸
I'm going to peel off your faces
-再慢慢吸干你们的血  -听我们说
- and drink you slowly. - Just listen.
你需要我们
You need us.
没错  我饥渴着呢
Oh, yes. I am thirsty!
这场瘟疫  我们知道是什么造成的
The plague! We know what it is!
你了解利维坦这东西吗
What do you know about Leviathan?
略知一二
A bit.
你知道他们给你们的食物投毒
You know they're poisoning the food supply?
我去年秋天和罗曼共进晚餐时他没提及这点
Roman didn't mention that when we met for dinner last fall.
我们制定了很多计划
We made lots of plans.
我和他  关系好得很呢
We are on excellent terms, he and I.
你确定
You sure about that?
他有没有提到  他会
Did he mention that he was going to...
毒害全人类
maui wowie the human population?
当然
Oh, of course.
他说觅食会史无前例的方便
He said grabbing a snack would be easier than ever.
他说你们会相亲相爱一辈子  对吧
He said you'd all live together, didn't he?
你还真信他
You really believe him?
你以为你的孩子们是意外死亡吗
You think your children are dying by accident?
婴儿食品里都有毒药
There is pesticide in the formula!
你们这么想也无可厚非
It suits you to think so.
你们需要我站在你们这边
You need me on your side.
又不是我们被从里面烧穿了
Look, we're not the ones burning from the inside out.
好好想想吧
Think about it.
他和你订的协议都是狗屁
Whatever deal he made with you was crap!
-相信我们  -你们为什么和我说这些
- Trust us! - Why are you telling me this?
因为我们能阻止迪克
Because we can stop Dick.
阻止整件事  我们只是
Stop all of it. We just...
需要你的血  来做武器
We need your blood-- for the weapon.
你们现在想防止
So now you want to prevent
吸血鬼一族的灭绝
the extermination of the vampire race.
不是
No.
但总比和你们一起死的好
But it beats going down with you.
艾伦  亲爱的
Allan, darling...
过来
Come.
真是越来越反胃了
Well, the creep gets creepier.
-怎么了  -埃德加来了
- What's wrong? - Edgar's here.
真巧啊
Wow, what a funny coincidence.
我们需要肥皂  清洁剂
All right, we need soap, uh, cleanser,
有硼砂的都行
anything with borax in it.
我们还要刀
We need knives.
把他们关进书房
Put them in the study.
什么  不  等等
What? No, no, no. No, wait.
-不  等下  -给你们个建议  孩子们
- No, wait. - Word of advice, boys.
我活过了几个世纪的极冷和极热的气候
You do not live through centuries of fire and ice
经历了大陆分裂
and continental divide...
那可不是靠妄下结论做到的
by jumping to conclusions.
好吧
Okay.
你在犯傻
You're making a mistake!
听我说  等等
Listen! Wait!
先了解情况总是好的
Never hurts to get the story first.
埃德加
Edgar.
早知道你来  就给你准备美味了
I would've whipped you up a meal.
请坐
Please, sit.
很想知道你为什么要来
I'm dying to know why you're here.
你知道的
I think you know.
怎讲
And how is that?
我闻到了温家双煞的味道
I smell Sam and Dean Winchester.
有发现吗
Anything?
没
Nothing.
你说埃德加来这儿的目的跟我们一样吗
You think Edgar's here for the same reason we are?
如果他们发现我们是为了
I mean, look, if they figured out
拿始祖的血做武器
that we're here to get Alpha blood for a weapon...
我认为不管怎么想
I think any way you slice it,
吃豆人和《真爱如血》放在一起
you got Pac Man and True Blood in the same room,
总没好事
and that's bad news.
他又不笨
I mean, he's not stupid.
干嘛要把我们关在这里呢
Why the hell do you think he locked us in here?
迪恩  我们可是他的敌人
Dean, we're his enemy.
他们这些怪物可是一家亲
I mean, they're like monster cousins or something.
换做是你  你愿意相信谁
Who would you give the benefit of the doubt to?
说不定苏克食品毒死吸血鬼就是意外
Now you know what? Maybe the Sucro is poisoning the vamps on accident.
他们可能会解决这个问题
Maybe they'll fix it.
我认为他以地球上最古老的怪物自居
I think you got the oldest monster on earth,
认为自己战无不胜  因为他一直没遇到对手
thinking he can hold his own because he always has.
埃德加会把他生吞了
Edgar's gonna eat him alive.
对啊
Yeah.
你能用这个撬锁吗
You think you could pick a lock with this?
但是  迪恩
But, Dean...
我们的吸血鬼毒液都被收走了
We gave up all our vamptonite.
是吗
Did we?
你想要那俩小子吗
Do you want the boys?
是吧
Yes?
随便你
You're welcome to them.
我这就找人带他们出来
I'll have them sent out.
谢谢啊
How kind of you.
但是  埃德加
Oh, Edgar...
你知道萨姆和迪恩来这儿干嘛吧
You do know why Sam and Dean are here, don't you?
他们坚称你们想把我们赶尽杀绝
They insist that you're exterminating us,
但我想  这不可能啊
and I thought, well, that's...impossible.
他们肯定搞错了
Must be a mistake.
你想得没错  当然不可能
You're right. Of course.
还真是吸血鬼毒液
Vamptonite.
绝对的
Friggin' vamptonite.
好了  咱们需要刀子
All right, we need knives.
这里肯定有储备室或厨房之类的  赶紧
There's got to be a prep room or a kitchen somewhere. Come on.
但我有点不明白  埃德加
Here's what I don't understand, Edgar.
你们知道那个小添加剂有些副作用吧
You are aware that your little additive has side effects, yes?
迪克警告过你可能会有设计缺陷
Dick warned you there might be kinks.
是  他还说会跟我联系
Yes. He also said he'd be in touch.
我的孩子们都很惊恐
My children are in a panic.
你们电话也不打一个  也不给个信
You don't call, you don't write,
也不送点礼问候一下啥的
you don't send cookies.
你们打算平息这场瘟疫吗
Where exactly on the list is fixing our plague?
亲爱的朋友
My dear friend...
没这打算
...nowhere.
我们想让你们像小强一样烧死
We want you to burn like the little roaches you are.
罗曼说只要我不插手  自然有我的好处
Roman said if I kept quiet, I would get my reward.
那你现在只能乖乖等死了
And now you get to lay down and die.
不是针对你们
Nothing personal.
我们的添加剂还能杀死狼人
Our additive kills the wolves, too...
变形怪  和那些吃尸体的恶心的小怪物
the shifters, and those disgusting little things that eat corpses.
只要是以人类为食的统统都会毒死
Anything with a taste for human.
只除了我们
Except us.
怎么说人类都是有限资源
Mankind's a limited resource, after all.
有七十亿人呢
There are seven billion... of them.
只有七十亿
Only seven.
-我们是你们的后代  -算不上
- We come from you. - Barely.
我是夏娃之子
I am the son of Eve!
就是个可怜的小杂种
A pathetic mutt.
有什么资格跟我们并列
Hardly one of us.
我认识夏娃
I knew Eve,
跟你说句大实话
and honestly...
你的老娘就是个婊子
your mommy was a whore.
别扭来扭曲  一滴血都不能落
Don't squirm. I need every last drop.
拿个杯子  榨他的血
Grab a glass. We're juicing this freak.
不要
No!
退后
Stay back!
别碰她
Leave her alone.
她受了不少苦
She's been through quite enough.
你还说这话
Now, that's rich...
是你把她从秋千上绑走的
coming from the guy who took her off the swing-set.
你们是想跟我打一架呢
Do you want to do this fight?
还是想要我的血
Or do you want my blood?
谢谢你们帮我搞定了埃德加
For taking care of Edgar.
现在可以滚了
Now go.
那个小男孩呢
What about the little boy?
你在开玩笑吧
Are you joking?
看起来像吗
Do we look like we're joking?
你这儿还有多少小孩  变态
How many other kids you got in here, you freak?
这会儿就他一个
At the moment, just him.
爱米莉
Emily...
帮艾伦穿好外套
help Allan with his coat.
他要跟萨姆和迪恩一起走
He's leaving with Sam and Dean.
拿去吧
Now, take it.
有没有搞错  连个谢谢都不说
What? No "Thank you"?
对哦对哦
Oh, right, right.
你们这会儿血脉贲张
Your flesh is crawling.
现在只想宰了我
All you really want to do is kill me now.
一想到还得伺机再来  就气得不行
You hate having to wait and come back and try again.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
你还是赶快把身体和头分开  拿得远远的
I wouldn't leave that head too close to that body for too long.
下季再见咯
See you next season.
我都等不及了
Looking forward to it.
咱们以后可别再这么做了
Let's never do that again.
警察以为是我们绑架了小孩
Cops thought we took that kid.
只要他能回家
Long as he gets back to his folks,
我才不管别人怎么想
I don't care what they thought.
我们还得跳窗啊  老兄
We had to jump out a freakin' window, man.
鲍比
Bobby.
Bobby?!
迪恩
Dean?
他走了
He's gone.
能测到一些电磁反应  但是消散得很快
I'm getting trace bits of EMF, but it's fading fast.
鲍比可能已经离开三四个小时了
And Bobby's probably been gone three or four hours.
他把酒瓶拿走了  迪恩
He's got the flask, Dean.
我们现在要怎么找他啊
How the hell are we supposed to track him?
我不想说的  但是
Look, I hate to say this, but...
那就别说了  他走了
Well, then don't. He's gone.
他怎么能这会儿来这一出呢
How could he do this... Now?
咱们已经拿到一半的武器材料
I mean, we've got half the freakin' weapon,
-马上就要成功了  -那已经不是他了
- we're almost there. - It's not him.
他已经不在思考了
I mean, he's not thinking.
那我们就自顾自的  任他在外面游荡吗
So, what, we just keep going while he's out there like this?
有别的选择吗
Do we have any other option?
他想要我们这么做的  对吧
I mean, it's what he'd want us to do. Right?
是啊
Yeah.
是  他  弗兰克  还有小卡
Yeah, him and Frank and Cass,
如果他的头脑还算清醒
if his marbles were in the bag.
好在咱们还能找克劳力  是吧
It's a good thing we got Crowley in our corner. Right?
看来最后总是得靠他
Seeing as how it all comes down to him.
肯定万无一失了
What could possibly go wrong?
你好啊
Hello...
迪克
...Dick.
克劳力先生
Mr. Crowley,
咱们好好谈谈吧
we have so much to talk about.
请坐
Take a seat.